[{"answer": "It's possible if it's real.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 6, "question": "Is it possible this could avert a US military strike on Syria?", "qSentId": 5}, {"answer": "If in fact that happened.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "Is military strike on pause?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, that is the challenge of the day, Piers.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Jessica, I can't really get laid around all this, can you try and tell me in simple, plain English where we are in terms of America's position on Syria?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, and isn't it from the question you raised and I think that the most senior official in government are where you are.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "I mean, here's my -- I suppose my reaction of this which is if you assume that Assad did unleash these chemical weapons slaughtering 400 children and over a thousand adults and his own people, if you take that assumption, why would you trust that kind of man to hand over his weapons and why would America trust Vladimir Putin in all of these?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "First of all, it's an issue that has been discussed in private for a long time.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "I just don't believe that's how this all at it was, isn't it?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "I mean, why does this leave the voting position here?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, it underscores the fact that the administration has not come up with any plausible means to prevent another attack while diplomacy like this may very well accomplish that.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Well, it's the public that ends up paying for it and the public that ends up bleeding for it.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "But of course, public opinion being against something like this isn't necessarily the sole reason why you would choose to do it or not if you're a President of a country like the United States, isn't it?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Right, there was an interruption from (inaudible).", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Can you hear me?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, of course that's not where we are but the answer is no.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Would you then support military action?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "You should expect everything.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Will there be attacks against American bases in the Middle East if there's an air strike?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Frankly, I don't think it is and this is about much more than the use of chemical weapons.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Is that the sensible way for America to go?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Well, look I think he's exploring it.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "And if the answer is they shouldn't, why is President Obama going along with it?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, I do think that, you know, history kind of rhymes but it doesn't exactly repeat itself.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "And what do you make of hearing the likes of Paul Wolfowitz outlining why we should be piling straight back into Syria given what we now know about the reality of Saddam Hussein's non-existent WMD?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "I think it's a concern we might have.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Do you think that's a fair criticism?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Is something brand-new that just knocks your socks off?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Yes, he is.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Is he still there?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "No, he's in his car and he continually has his hand on his gun and he keep saying, \"Step closer.\"", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Is he inside now?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "And he's going to shoot us.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Saying step closer and what?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Good to be here, Piers.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Emily Miller, how are you?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "My boys (inaudible) second amendment, I'm not conservative.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Tell me what happened?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "I talked him out.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "How did you defend yourself against that one guy?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "I wouldn't prefer to shoot.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "So, why would you prefer to shoot him?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Well, (inaudible) is like -- I mean ...", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "2 million times a year in America, and yet I never read any examples, where are they?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, there's a bias in the liberal media against showing these kinds of stories.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "When were all these things happening?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Not my paper Washington.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "So is every paper in America liberal media?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "He doesn't care about the blind people.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "You want to stop people killing each other, right?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Can I talk?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "It hasn't happened yet.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "It's something that's going to happen?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "It's been fully legal in most states right now and they're not doing it because gun owners are responsible, which they train responsibly, which they store responsibly.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Do you think blind people are going to accidentally shoot people?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "I'm going to tell you what.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "You actually think that we can have responsible blind gun owners?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Well, the gun lobby (ph) is not -- the gun always now doing that is the disability groups who actually the ones advocating for this.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "It is ridiculous?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Emily Gets Her Gun But Obama Wants to Take Yours, Emily Miller, the Senior Editor of the Washington Times, good to meet you.", "docId": "130909pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "That's not mine, right?", "qSentId": 478}]